

MEGUMI KIMURA Frontend Developer

CONTACT

+47 48384765

kimuramegumi@gmail.com

23 Snøklokkeveien 1475 (Lørenskog)

LINK

LinkedIn GitHub Portfolio

SUMMARY

As a curious and passionate frontend developer, I have recently graduated from a 2-year web development program at Noroff with top grades. I have a deep passion for coding and UX design, and I'm dedicated to continuous learning and growth. My diverse background in international finance and shipping has provided me with a unique perspective that I bring to projects and workplaces. In addition to my technical skills, I possess valuable soft skills for effective collaboration with various stakeholders. I am currently seeking opportunities to apply my skills and enthusiasm to exciting projects.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Language HTML / CSS / JavaScript / Type Script / Python /SQL

Framework Svelte / React / Bootstrap / Tailwind

Workflow/Methodology Agile Method / GitHub / GitHub Project / Github Action / Trello / UX Design

REST APIs / Shell / Postman / Figma / WP / Cypress / Jest

EDUCATIONS

Others

Oct 2021 – Oct 2023 Frontend Development

Noroff School of technology and digital media

Aug 2011 – Feb 2014 M.A. International Development Studies

Norwegian University of Life Sciences (NMBU)

Apr 2004 – Mar 2007 B.A. International Law

Rikkyo University (Tokyo)

LATEST PROJECTS

Side project <u>Čika Petar's</u>

<u>github repo</u> Cocktail recipe app

Stack: Svelte • TypeScript • Tailwind • Skeleton UI • Vite

Features: Search, Save, lookup by ingredients

Open Source Project

github repo

Mollify

Educational platform

Stack: Sveltekit • TypeScript • Tailwind • Skeleton UI • Vite • Open AI

Features: Search, Bookmark, Speech to Text, Al chatbot

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

Aug 2022 - Dec 2022 Oslo	 Conference Assistant NORWEGIAN RED CROSS (Humanitarian organisation) Coordinate closely with organizers/suppliers and handle daily operations Ensure that the guests are satisfied and make events successful
Apr 2021 – Jul 2022 Tønsberg	Office Manager CRYPHO (IT) Invoicing / Financial reportings to the investors Ensure company's GDPR compliance
Apr 2017 – Oct 2017 Tønsberg	 Junior Shipbroker HESNES GAS (Shipping/Gas) Daily communications with clients on operations/chartering Following up with freight payment / calculations / dispute
Jun 2014 – Jun 2016 Tokyo	 Institutional Client Service COHEN & STEERS (Finance/Asset Management) Servicing clients (asset managers) via investment reporting, marketing Daily communication with NY team and Japanese clients, translation
Jun 2008 – Jun 2011 Mumbai	 Corporate Access DAIWA CAPITAL MARKETS INDIA (Finans/Børsmarked) Coordinate with various stakeholders to promote investment to India Managing projects: investment conferences, research tours, corporate meetings
LANGUAGES	English, Norwegian, Japanese
CEDTIFICATES	Migrosoft A7 000 (20 02 2022)

CERTIFICATES Microsoft AZ 900 (30.03.2023)

VOLUNTEERING Veileder - Frivillig Arbeid i Røde Kors Kvinnesenter Tønsberg

PUBLICATIONS YouTube video PostgreSQL | psql for beginners april 2023

(created and published for fellow students)

HOBBIES Capoeira (Brazilian Martial Arts), Saxophone